<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ankit Tyagi</title>
    <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ankit Tyagi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© Ankit Tyagi 2021</copyright><atom:link href="https://antyagi5.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 22:08:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antyagi5.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications  Impact of turbulence on the coherent flame dynamics in a bluff-body stabilized flame A Karmarkar, A Tyagi, S Hemchandra, J O’Connor, Proceedings of the Combustion Institute, 2020  Towards a method of estimating out-of-plane effects on measurements of turbulent flame dynamics A Tyagi, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Combustion and Flame, 2020  Development of a Diagnostic Damkohler Number for Interpreting Laser-Induced Fluorescence Data in Turbulent Flames K Beseler, A Tyagi, JA O&amp;rsquo;Connor, AIAA Scitech 2020 Forum, 2020  Pocket formation and behavior in turbulent premixed flames A Tyagi, I Boxx, S Peluso, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Combustion and Flame, 2020  Flame Edge Dynamics and Interaction in a Multi-nozzle Can Combustor with Fuel Staging D Doleiden, W Culler, A Tyagi, S Peluso, J O’Connor, ournal of Engineering for Gas Turbines and Power, 2019  Statistics and topology of local flame–flame interactions in turbulent flames A Tyagi, I Boxx, S Peluso, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Combustion and Flame, 2019  Identifying Complex Dynamics of Interacting Turbulent Jets through Modal Decompositions M Meehan, NT Wimer, A Tyagi, JA O&amp;rsquo;Connor, P Hamlington, AIAA Scitech 2019 Forum, 2019  Two-dimensional modeling for physical processes in direct flame fuel cells J Kim, A Tyagi, Y Kim, International Journal of Hydrogen Energy, 2019  Statistics of local flame-flame interactions in flame interaction zones of two V-flames A Tyagi, IG Boxx, S Peluso, JA O&amp;rsquo;Connor, AIAA Scitech 2019 Forum,	2019  The role of flow interaction in flame–flame interaction events in a dual burner experiment A Tyagi, I Boxx, S Peluso, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Proceedings of the Combustion Institute 37, 2019  Flow dynamics in a variable-spacing, three bluff-body flowfield M Meehan, A Tyagi, J O’Connor, Physics of Fluids,	2018  The Effects of Piloting on Turbulent Flame Structure R Shupp, A Tyagi, I Boxx, S Peluso, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Technical Meeting of the Eastern States Section of The Combustion Institute, 2018  Topology of Local Flame-Flame Interaction Events in Turbulent Flames A Tyagi, I Boxx, S Peluso, R Shupp, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Technical Meeting of the Eastern States Section of The Combustion Institute, 2018  Structure of flames in flame interaction zones A Tyagi, IG Boxx, SJ Peluso, R Shupp, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, 2018 AIAA Aerospace Sciences Meeting, 2018  Comparison of Three Interacting V-Flames to a Single Bluff-Body Flame at Two Reynolds Numbers W Culler, A Tyagi, P Venkateswaran, JA OConnor, 54th AIAA Aerospace Sciences Meeting, 2016   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolstuff</title>
      <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/coolstuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 22:08:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antyagi5.github.io/coolstuff/</guid>
      <description>Cool Stuff This is where some of the cool stuff I am working on will be posted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 21:52:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antyagi5.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A Mechanical Engineer by training, I hold a Ph.D. focused on Experimental Combustion research. I currently work at Eriez Manufacturing as an R&amp;amp;D Digital Signal Processing Engineer and have experience working as a Process Engineer at Intel Corporation. Through the academic and industry roles that I have navigated so far, I have developed a strong skill set in experimental research, metrology, and advanced data analysis methods. My recent interests include: • Digital image and signal processing methods • Statistical data analysis, probabilistic modeling, computational problem solving • Laser diagnostics/metrology and imaging techniques • The art of espresso</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
