<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ankit Tyagi</title>
    <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ankit Tyagi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© Ankit Tyagi 2021</copyright><atom:link href="https://antyagi5.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 22:08:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antyagi5.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications  &amp;ldquo;Impact of turbulence on the coherent flame dynamics in a bluff-body stabilized flame&amp;rdquo;, A Karmarkar, A Tyagi, S Hemchandra, J O’Connor, Proceedings of the Combustion Institute, 2020. Link  &amp;ldquo;Towards a method of estimating out-of-plane effects on measurements of turbulent flame dynamics&amp;rdquo;, A Tyagi, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, Combustion and Flame, 2020. Link | PDF  &amp;ldquo;Development of a Diagnostic Damkohler Number for Interpreting Laser-Induced Fluorescence Data in Turbulent Flames&amp;rdquo;, K Beseler, A Tyagi, J O&amp;rsquo;Connor, AIAA Scitech 2020 Forum, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolstuff</title>
      <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/coolstuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 22:08:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antyagi5.github.io/coolstuff/</guid>
      <description>Cool Stuff This is where some of the cool stuff I am working on will be posted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://antyagi5.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 21:52:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antyagi5.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A Mechanical Engineer by training, I hold a Ph.D. focused on Experimental Combustion research. I currently work at Eriez Manufacturing as an R&amp;amp;D Digital Signal Processing Engineer and have experience working as a Process Engineer at Intel Corporation. Through the academic and industry roles that I have navigated so far, I have developed a strong skill set in experimental research, metrology, and advanced data analysis methods. My recent interests include: • Digital image and signal processing methods • Statistical data analysis, probabilistic modeling, computational problem solving • Laser diagnostics, metrology, imaging techniques • The art of espresso</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
